[Music]
[音乐]
此卡是一个弹出式窗口，可以
this card is a pop-up house that can be
用作生日贺卡或
搬家卡或其他任何东西
this card is a pop-up house that can be
used either as a birthday card or a
可能会认为它是基于正确的
角v形和平行四边形，如果
used either as a birthday card or a
moving house cards or anything else you
我们看这是潜在的
打开时会看到的结构
moving house cards or anything else you
might think of it's based on the right
关闭，这是直角v形折叠
这就是你的平行四边形
might think of it's based on the right
angle v-fold and the parallelogram so if
打开和关闭平行四边形
抬起所有的墙壁，所以扭曲
angle v-fold and the parallelogram so if
we look at this this is the underlying
将屋顶固定在屋顶上
固定在这两个侧壁上
we look at this this is the underlying
structure you'll see as it opens and
彼此相对扭曲
关闭仅留下的点
structure you'll see as it opens and
closes this is the right angle v-fold
彼此相同的是
两个山墙末端，以便为您添加屋顶
closes this is the right angle v-fold
and this is the parallelogram as you
必须在其中建一个屋顶梁
我只是举起你可以看到
and this is the parallelogram as you
open and close it the parallelogram
连接两个山墙的屋顶梁
末端，屋顶粘在那些
open and close it the parallelogram
lifts up all the walls twists around so
接近为屋顶固定的标签
这将需要测量，所以
lifts up all the walls twists around so
fixing a roof onto it the roof can't be
需要的工具需要胶水
你需要一把尺子，你需要剪刀
fixing a roof onto it the roof can't be
fixed to this two side walls as they
然后设置正方形
实际使用一张卡作为一组
fixed to this two side walls as they
twist in relation to each other as it
方，稍后我会解释
这是测量的模板
twist in relation to each other as it
closes the only points that stay the
我将在这里再次绘制
一分钟就把它剪下来，这样你就可以
closes the only points that stay the
same in relation to each other are the
看到这里这些长度短
墙壁他们是四个半
same in relation to each other are the
two gable ends so to add the roof you
厘米
长墙是7厘米
two gable ends so to add the roof you
have to build a roof beam into it so if
您有一个1厘米的标签，
另一头在这里拉
have to build a roof beam into it so if
I just lift this up you can see there's
变圆并变成一个矩形
我在这里画了，这是底部
I just lift this up you can see there's
a roof beam that joins the two gable
行，你需要得分，所以我想
那是您需要的另一个工具是
a roof beam that joins the two gable
ends and the roof sticks onto those
圆珠笔或类似的东西和
所以你需要在这里得分
ends and the roof sticks onto those
nears the tabs holding the roof on for
两个标签
您还需要在这里评分
nears the tabs holding the roof on for
this you will need to measure so the
该选项卡将整个事情拉到一个
矩形去
this you will need to measure so the
tools you'll need you'll need glue
您还需要一个顶梁，这样
屋顶梁我实际上已经做到了三
tools you'll need you'll need glue
you'll need a ruler you'll need scissors
厘米高，但不是真的
重要的一遍，你需要得分
you'll need a ruler you'll need scissors
and set square alternatively you can
这里，因为这是一个标签，这里
是这些标签要粘贴的标签
and set square alternatively you can
actually use a piece of card as a set
山墙结束，然后沿着顶部
是的，您将有两个标签
actually use a piece of card as a set
square and I'll explain that in a minute
在这里，所以你需要为此评分
线，以便那些折叠很好
square and I'll explain that in a minute
here's the template the measurements are
如果您没有三角板，可以
用一张纸牌的一个角
here's the template the measurements are
I've drawn it up again here I'm going to
90度角，所以当你来
要测量，您将需要标尺
I've drawn it up again here I'm going to
cut this one out in a minute so you can
在这里测量这些距离，但是你
然后可以使用一块
cut this one out in a minute so you can
see here the these lengths the short
卡只是为了给你这些权利
立柱到达的角度和此处
see here the these lengths the short
walls they're four and a half
以及，所以我会把它切掉
快速，您可以使用一对
walls they're four and a half
centimeters
剪刀，或者你可以用手工生活
像这样，我发现工艺刀是
the long walls are 7 centimeters
最快的方法我就剪掉
出来真的很快
you've got a 1 centimetre tab and
所以这是房子的基本件
确保所有这些角落都是真的
you've got a 1 centimetre tab and
another one on the end here that pulls
好
一如既往地皱折
another one on the end here that pulls
it round and turns it into a rectangle
向后和向前折叠
自己一次又一次地折皱
it round and turns it into a rectangle
I've drawn it up here this is the bottom
让他们都真正舒适地移动
弹出窗口打开和关闭时
I've drawn it up here this is the bottom
line you will need to score so I suppose
并确实折起标签
彻底地，然后我就把它全部打了
line you will need to score so I suppose
that's another tool you'll need is a
理想的是用墨斗
你会用圆珠笔知道
that's another tool you'll need is a
ballpoint pen or something similar and
但是随着墨水的渗入，
这些线，所以当您将其折叠成
ballpoint pen or something similar and
so you'll need to score along here where
半形确保那些折线
在里面，这个标签是
so you'll need to score along here where
the two tabs go
把所有东西都放在一起
里面只是放一些胶水
the two tabs go
you'll also need to score up here where
胶合后，请确保
整个东西实际上会放平，所以
you'll also need to score up here where
the tab pulling the whole thing into a
您可以尝试两种方式，然后
需要一张底纸，将其对折
the tab pulling the whole thing into a
rectangle goes
再次彻底地彻底折皱
这需要确保选项卡
rectangle goes
you'll also need a roof beam so this
两者都与脊椎成45度角
不要将它贴在角落上
you'll also need a roof beam so this
roof beam I've actually made it three
您必须将它与
脊椎所以你可以使用一套
roof beam I've actually made it three
centimetres high but it doesn't really
广场给你的指导方针
像这样把它们画出来，所以你知道
centimetres high but it doesn't really
matter and again you'll need to score
你要坚持的地方
向下或再次，您可以使用像
matter and again you'll need to score
here because this is a tab and here this
这是一张卡片上的，这样你
知道这是90度的折痕
here because this is a tab and here this
is a tab these are going to stick onto
一半，所以边缘在旁边
彼此会给你两个
is a tab these are going to stick onto
the gable ends and then along the top
45度极点，然后您可以将其
与中央对齐
the gable ends and then along the top
here yeah you're going to have two tabs
折痕，您可以用它来标记
你要去哪里
here yeah you're going to have two tabs
here and so you'll need to score this
因为一切都经过测量，您可以
实际上将双方都朝下
here and so you'll need to score this
line so that those fold down nicely so
同时确保选项卡
当它进入时按住它
line so that those fold down nicely so
if you haven't got a set square you can
他们不重叠的位置，所以在此
你可以看到它们有点大，所以我
if you haven't got a set square you can
use a corner of a sheet of card this is
只是要剪掉额外的一块
那些不会在脊柱上重叠
use a corner of a sheet of card this is
a 90 degree angle and so when you come
现在我们可以把它们都压在
一如既往地用胶水
a 90 degree angle and so when you come
to measuring up you will need the ruler
折痕很重要，所以你
确保胶水正确
to measuring up you will need the ruler
to measure these distances here but you
折痕，然后可以将其定位
所以那些折痕都在那些
to measure these distances here but you
can then use a the corner of a piece of
准则，然后像所有弹出窗口一样
折叠起来
can then use a the corner of a piece of
cards just to give you these right
用力按下以确保
它被牢固地压住了，所以有
cards just to give you these right
angles where the uprights come and here
现在房子的开始
拿到屋顶梁，确保所有
angles where the uprights come and here
as well so I'll just cut this out really
折痕确实得到很好的加固
前后折叠然后
as well so I'll just cut this out really
quickly you can either use a pair of
重要的是当你
坚持下去，它将坚持下去
quickly you can either use a pair of
scissors or you can use a craft life
山墙结束了这些折痕
垂直的，所以您可以将它们都粘在
scissors or you can use a craft life
like this so I find craft knives are the
同时，只要确保
折痕垂直上升到
like this so I find craft knives are the
the quickest way to go I'll just cut it
山墙末端的最尖端
同样，我们可以将胶水涂在这两个
the quickest way to go I'll just cut it
out really fast
同时我不认为
实际上有什么不同，但我
so here's the basic piece for the house
将有一种指向一种方式，
一个指向另一种方式只是给
so here's the basic piece for the house
make sure all these corners are really
它有些对称，并再次确保
胶水直达
make sure all these corners are really
well
折痕然后你就可以放
像那样的地方
well
creased as always just fold them
确保这两个的折痕
排名靠前的排名靠前
creased as always just fold them
backwards and forwards fold them on
我们将其关闭以确保
一切就绪，整个
backwards and forwards fold them on
themselves crease them again and again
找到东西
在那里，然后当我们把
themselves crease them again and again
so that they all move really comfortably
屋顶将要下降
这些将一分重量
so that they all move really comfortably
when the pop-up is opening and closing
一个会走另一条路
这是屋顶的一块折痕
and also crease the tabs really
在中间确保那是真的
折叠好，尺寸好
and also crease the tabs really
thoroughly and then I've scored it all
屋顶的长度将是
沿着这边是8,5厘米
thoroughly and then I've scored it all
with a barrow with ink in it ideally
屋顶的宽度是5,5
5,5所以这正沿着
with a barrow with ink in it ideally
you'd use a ballpoint pen with knowing
屋顶，所以我们将其对折
这些的另一点是
you'd use a ballpoint pen with knowing
but as it has got ink in it you've got
基地关闭屋顶的角落有
有进入页面的趋势，所以我
but as it has got ink in it you've got
these lines so when you fold it into the
只是跑掉他们，所以你可以做到
用它折成两半就围绕他们
these lines so when you fold it into the
half shape make sure those folded lines
以便它可以更轻松地移动
然后把胶水放在两个屋顶梁上
half shape make sure those folded lines
are inside and also this tab that's
标签，即使在这里，然后你只需要
靠眼睛放置屋顶我会涂抹
are inside and also this tab that's
holding it all together you put that on
胶保持尺寸或任何
在它下面画线或测量
holding it all together you put that on
the inside just put some glue on that
向上，所以两端等距
超过山墙，确保折痕
once you've glued it make sure that the
顶部与它齐平
看起来对我合适然后关闭
once you've glued it make sure that the
whole thing will actually lie flat so
整个底座洗净并在那里
你有它那里有你的房子
whole thing will actually lie flat so
you can try it both ways and then you'll
我没有提到的维度是这个
在房子的角落和
you can try it both ways and then you'll
need a base sheet so fold it in half
此处的底面需要6厘米
就在
need a base sheet so fold it in half
crease it really thoroughly again and on
那是六个，所以房子基本上是
平行四边形，在这种情况下是
crease it really thoroughly again and on
this you need to be sure that the tabs
平行四边形建立在v形折叠上，但是
还有其他方法可以玩
this you need to be sure that the tabs
both up 45 degrees to the spine you
因此，在此示例中，
它成直角v形折叠
both up 45 degrees to the spine you
don't stick it on corner to corner
您可以将其构建为锯齿形的折痕
之字形折叠是教程20，
don't stick it on corner to corner
you have to have it 45 degrees to the
房屋又是一样的
我把屋顶梁放在下面
you have to have it 45 degrees to the
spine so again you can either use a set
给你看一下曲折
折痕是基于
spine so again you can either use a set
square to give you the the guide lines
平行四边形这是常规的锯齿形
折叠所以这是给你三个
square to give you the the guide lines
like this just draw them on so you know
您可以内置的沟渠可以
建在这里和这里如此
like this just draw them on so you know
where you're going to be sticking it
如果房子不粘到
把房子粘进去
where you're going to be sticking it
down or again you can use a corner like
订购房子，我只会解释一下
在这种情况下，尺寸为
down or again you can use a corner like
this from a piece of card so that you
基于平行四边形
在这种情况下，它粘的地方
this from a piece of card so that you
know this is a 90 degree fold so fold
他们都指向同一点
脊椎，然后从这个距离
know this is a 90 degree fold so fold
that in half so the edges are next to
脊椎的角落与此相同
短边，这很长的距离
that in half so the edges are next to
each other that will give you two
在角落和脊椎之间是
和现在这里的长人一样
each other that will give you two
45-degree poles so then you can put that
建造了你可以实际建造的房子
因此，如果我们看看这个
45-degree poles so then you can put that
in line up the fold with the central
罗伯茨佛陀的奇妙巫师
盎司真的很棒
in line up the fold with the central
crease and you can use that to mark
里面的房子有点不同
这里的房子风格是你可以看到
crease and you can use that to mark
where you're going
他的工作方式是卡住了
屋顶的边缘实际上被粘到了
where you're going
since it's all measured up you can
房子的墙壁，所以这意味着
因为当你关闭时一切都会旋转
since it's all measured up you can
actually stick both sides down at the
它没有合适的屋脊
房屋开闭时您会看到
actually stick both sides down at the
same time make sure that the tabs
屋顶移动，所以这是分裂
发现不太满意，这就是为什么
same time make sure that the tabs
holding it down that when it's in
我更喜欢这种其他方式，但
关于宿雾的真正好事
holding it down that when it's in
position they don't overlap so on this
这些是在这里做的树
房屋关闭时进入房屋
position they don't overlap so on this
you can see they're slightly big so I'm
有两个沟壑论坛不会沟壑
在这条长边上，另一边
you can see they're slightly big so I'm
just going to snip an extra piece off
沟壑在这里
这样您就可以内置到这些沟渠中
just going to snip an extra piece off
those so they don't overlap on the spine
在这种情况下，这是一个平行四边形，
然后这棵树是由两个
now we can stick them both down at the
平行四边形和槽正在上升
保持这些层次真的
now we can stick them both down at the
same time as always with glue the
聪明的是寂寞的沟壑
房子的短边
same time as always with glue the
creases are the important thing so you
他在其中建立了平行四边形
沟，然后那个平行四边形
creases are the important thing so you
make sure that the glue goes right up to
侧面它沿着这里延伸，所以你已经
得到这棵树这些是平行四边形
make sure that the glue goes right up to
the creases and then you can position it
实际上解决了沟壑
在另一边，就是这样
the creases and then you can position it
so both those creases are on those
制作房卡
[音乐]
so both those creases are on those
guidelines and then as with all pop ups
[掌声]
[音乐]
guidelines and then as with all pop ups
fold it shut